trendrr.com 2018-10-22

# Privacy Policy | Trendrr

**Privacy Policy**

We do respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

 **Log Files**

Like most standard Web sites Trendrr (trendrr.net) makes use of log files. This information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to personally identifiable information.

 **Cookies**

Trendrr does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. We do use also third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you..

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Trendrr privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

 **Links**

You should take note that Trendrr contains links to other sites. Please be aware that World’s People’s Fortune Collection is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites and no control regarding the content or any information provided by these websites and cannot guarantee the reliability or accuracy of any information linked externally.We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Website.

 **Advertisers**

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process and are collected by our ad companies, we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: Google Adsense. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

####  **AMAZON AFFILIATE DISCLOSURE**

We are an affiliate of Amazon.in. In basic terminology, this means that we make a few percent of each sale we refer to them. This does not affect our positioning of products nor affect the price of the product(s) for you.

We get advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.in or Amazon.com

 **Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on any of our sites.

 **Notification of Changes**

Whenever we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy page, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

 **Contact Information**

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us through our [contact form](http://www.trendrr.net/contact-us/).
